[{"answer": " Hows your week going", "docId": "05-07", "aSentId": 13, "question": "", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " Its been OK.  Ive been going to all my classes and working 30 hours this week", "docId": "05-07", "aSentId": 14, "question": " Hows your week going", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " That seems like a lot", "docId": "05-07", "aSentId": 15, "question": " Its been OK.  Ive been going to all my classes and working 30 hours this week", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " I know.  I feel like Im stretched too thin.  I barely have time to study, and Im s", "docId": "05-07", "aSentId": 16, "question": " That seems like a lot", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " Cant you cut back on your hours at work a little bit", "docId": "05-07", "aSentId": 20, "question": " I know.  I feel like Im stretched too thin.  I barely have time to study, and Im s", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " I can a little.  Im going to try to work just 20 hours next week.  But, I cant reall", "docId": "05-07", "aSentId": 21, "question": " Cant you cut back on your hours at work a little bit", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " I hear you.  Im practically broke right now.  I really need to get a job", "docId": "05-07", "aSentId": 25, "question": " I can a little.  Im going to try to work just 20 hours next week.  But, I cant reall", "qSentId": 24},{"answer": " Have you been looking", "docId": "05-07", "aSentId": 26, "question": " I hear you.  Im practically broke right now.  I really need to get a job", "qSentId": 25},{"answer": " Not really.  I havent started looking yet.  Im gonna start this week.  Are they stil", "docId": "05-07", "aSentId": 27, "question": " Have you been looking", "qSentId": 26},{"answer": " No, all the positions are filled right now", "docId": "05-07", "aSentId": 33, "question": " Not really.  I havent started looking yet.  Im gonna start this week.  Are they stil", "qSentId": 32},{"answer": " Well, how did you find your job", "docId": "05-07", "aSentId": 34, "question": " No, all the positions are filled right now", "qSentId": 33},{"answer": " Actually, my friend works there, and he told me about an open position", "docId": "05-07", "aSentId": 35, "question": " Well, how did you find your job", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " Oh, OK.  Whats the best way to find a student job", "docId": "05-07", "aSentId": 36, "question": " Actually, my friend works there, and he told me about an open position", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " Before I got this job, I went to the career center on campus", "docId": "05-07", "aSentId": 37, "question": " Oh, OK.  Whats the best way to find a student job", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " Really?  I though they just helped students find jobs after they graduated", "docId": "05-07", "aSentId": 38, "question": " Before I got this job, I went to the career center on campus", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " They do that, but they also help students find part-time jobs while theyre i", "docId": "05-07", "aSentId": 39, "question": " Really?  I though they just helped students find jobs after they graduated", "qSentId": 38},{"answer": " I didnt know that", "docId": "05-07", "aSentId": 43, "question": " They do that, but they also help students find part-time jobs while theyre i", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " Yeah.  They have a website where you can search for available positions.  Plus", "docId": "05-07", "aSentId": 44, "question": " I didnt know that", "qSentId": 43},{"answer": " That sounds pretty helpful.  Ill have to check them out", "docId": "05-07", "aSentId": 48, "question": " Yeah.  They have a website where you can search for available positions.  Plus", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": " Its definitely a good place to start.  You can look around campus for flyers too.  ", "docId": "05-07", "aSentId": 49, "question": " That sounds pretty helpful.  Ill have to check them out", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " Thats a good point.  I always walk right past them without even looking.  I wa", "docId": "05-07", "aSentId": 53, "question": " Its definitely a good place to start.  You can look around campus for flyers too.  ", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " Sure.  My friend Bill found a job that way.  He just looked through the classifie", "docId": "05-07", "aSentId": 57, "question": " Thats a good point.  I always walk right past them without even looking.  I wa", "qSentId": 56},{"answer": " Ill have to pick up a paper today and have a look.  Hopefully, Ill find something", "docId": "05-07", "aSentId": 61, "question": " Sure.  My friend Bill found a job that way.  He just looked through the classifie", "qSentId": 60},{"answer": " There are a lot of jobs out there for students.  Another thing you can do is jus", "docId": "05-07", "aSentId": 62, "question": " Ill have to pick up a paper today and have a look.  Hopefully, Ill find something", "qSentId": 61},{"answer": " Thats a good idea, too.  Ill try that if I cant find a job with the paper and caree", "docId": "05-07", "aSentId": 66, "question": " There are a lot of jobs out there for students.  Another thing you can do is jus", "qSentId": 65},{"answer": " That sounds like a good plan.  So, how many hours a week do you want t", "docId": "05-07", "aSentId": 72, "question": " Thats a good idea, too.  Ill try that if I cant find a job with the paper and caree", "qSentId": 71},{"answer": " Im taking a lot of hard classes right now, so I need a lot of time to study.  I wa", "docId": "05-07", "aSentId": 74, "question": " That sounds like a good plan.  So, how many hours a week do you want t", "qSentId": 73},{"answer": " That sounds good.  You should still have time to study if you worked ten hours", "docId": "05-07", "aSentId": 80, "question": " Im taking a lot of hard classes right now, so I need a lot of time to study.  I wa", "qSentId": 79},{"answer": " I wont be making that much money, but every little bit will help", "docId": "05-07", "aSentId": 81, "question": " That sounds good.  You should still have time to study if you worked ten hours", "qSentId": 80},{"answer": " Sure.  You can use the money you make for food and entertainment", "docId": "05-07", "aSentId": 82, "question": " I wont be making that much money, but every little bit will help", "qSentId": 81},{"answer": " Right.  It could help pay for things like that", "docId": "05-07", "aSentId": 83, "question": " Sure.  You can use the money you make for food and entertainment", "qSentId": 82},{"answer": " Well, I hope you can find a job", "docId": "05-07", "aSentId": 84, "question": " Right.  It could help pay for things like that", "qSentId": 83},{"answer": " Me too", "docId": "05-07", "aSentId": 85, "question": " Well, I hope you can find a job", "qSentId": 84},{"answer": " Let me know how it goes", "docId": "05-07", "aSentId": 86, "question": " Me too", "qSentId": 85},{"answer": " OK, sure", "docId": "05-07", "aSentId": 87, "question": " Let me know how it goes", "qSentId": 86}]
